Leal Williams

07490 417826

lealjwilliams@gmail.com
https://lealwilliams.github.io/
linkedin.com/in/leal-williams-120783196

Sheffield Dinnington

About Me

I have recently graduated from Sheffield Hallam University with a 2:1 degree in Computer Science for Games, and I have now completed my first contract with Pearson. At Pearson, I efficiently worked across multiple roles ensuring my tasks were completed on time. At University, I have experienced working with a small team on multiple projects, working together to meet tight deadlines. I have contributed ideas towards the implementation of the systems that make the programs function and taken feedback from my peers on how I could improve my own work. I also worked on multiple tasks simultaneously for my other modules.

Experience

Pearson – Data Input 2023-2023

- Used internal software to document and input information thoroughly.
- Excellent use of Microsoft Excel to pick up and complete tasks on team spreadsheets.
- Resolved issues of documents, following instructions closely on how to resolve the most common issues.
- Utilizing the information that I learned, I became able to process new and unique tasks with less assistance from supervisors required.
- Worked on tasks individually, assisted other members of the team when needed, and asked peers for help when I was unsure on my own tasks.

Sheffield Hallam University – BSc – 2:1 – Computer Science for Games

2019-2022

- Attended regular scrum meetings with teammates and lecturers to discuss what goals we plan to achieve within the week and what we have accomplished in the last week.
- Updated my progress on Trello, showcasing how much time I have spent, and the total time left I
 predict I would spend on each task.
- Efficient use of GitHub for source control on each of my projects.
- Collaborated with Designers and Artists to realize their ideas into the project.
- Developed Games using an Object-Oriented Design, allowing the systems to efficiently be expanded with additional content.
- Contributed to Technical Design Documents detailing the systems I worked on.
- Experience in working on PS4 and PC games.
- Created a game by myself, using DirectXTK to create a 2D platformer using assets I created.
- Unity Group Project with a tight deadline of 6 weeks achieved.

Aardvark Swift Recruitment - Work Experience

2018-2018

- Used Bullhorn to input and update information in their database about clients.
- Consulted with employees in the office when an issue would arise.
- 4-day work experience

Leal Williams

07490 417826

<u>lealjwilliams@gmail.com</u> <u>https://lealwilliams.github.io/</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/leal-williams-120783196</u> Sheffield Dinnington

Education

Sheffield Hallam University

2019-2022

• BSc - 2:1 - Computer Science for Games

Thomas Rotherham College

2017-2019

- Achieved 4 A Levels:
 - o Maths (A)
 - o Further Maths (B)
 - o Computer Science (B)
 - o Physics (C)

Dinnington High School

2012-2017

• Achieved 9 GSCEs, (A-C), including English (6), Maths (8) and Science (A)

Key Skills

- Software
 - Visual Studio
 - Unity Engine 5
 - o Unreal Engine 4
 - o GitHub
 - o Autodesk 3DS Max
 - o Microsoft Office Suite
- Languages
 - o C++
 - o C#
 - o Lua
 - o Python
 - o HTML
 - o CSS
 - o .NET

Hobbies

- Game Development on Roblox
- Video Games

References available on request